BEN KOSHROVSKI

Personal info

Phone:

054-7835165

Email:

benkosh@gmail.com

Address:

Israel (IL)

Skills

English

Git

Redux

React

CSS

HTML

Javascript

Professional Summary

A highly motivated, self-taught Full Stack Web Developer with over 2 years experience developing web applications.

A passionate and hardworking team player eager to learn and contribute. Loves to break down and solve problems, face challenges, and turn ideas into reality. Always dedicated to run the extra mile.

You are more than welcome to visit my portfolio website at - www.benkosh.com.

Education

Ironi Yod Dalet, Tel Aviv, Israel

GED, Jun. 2011

Military Service

Sorting NCO

Israeli Air Force 2011-2014

-Received Certificate of Excellence for leading a project involving recruiting for less appealing army jobs.

Employment history

Club Manager, Plug-In. Tel Aviv

May. 2016 - Jun. 2020

Part of my job as a Karaoke club manager included -

- Investigate and resolve complaints regarding food quality, service, or accommodations.
- Coordinate assignments of cooking personnel to ensure economical use of food and timely preparation.
- Schedule and receive food and beverage deliveries, checking delivery contents to verify product quality and quantity.
- Organize and direct worker training programs, resolve personnel problems, hire new staff, and evaluate employee performance in dining and lodging facilities.
- Received worker of the year honorary.

Bar Manager, Black. Tel Aviv

Oct. 2014 - May. 2016